[{"answer": " Whats up, Sam?  How was your trip", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " It was great", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Whats up, Sam?  How was your trip", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Where did you go again, California", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " It was great", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " No, I went to Colorado.  The camp was in Boulder", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Where did you go again, California", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Cool.  What kind of camp was it", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " No, I went to Colorado.  The camp was in Boulder", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "It was an outdoor camp.  You know, we camped and did all kinds of outdoo", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Cool.  What kind of camp was it", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " What kind of stuff did you do", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 19, "question": "It was an outdoor camp.  You know, we camped and did all kinds of outdoo", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, the first day we went hiking though the mountains.  We hiked for 12 miles", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What kind of stuff did you do", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Did you have to carry a pack", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Well, the first day we went hiking though the mountains.  We hiked for 12 miles", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Yes, we had to carry a 20-pound pack for our food and supplies.  My back wa", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Did you have to carry a pack", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " I dont think I could last two miles, let alone twelve", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Yes, we had to carry a 20-pound pack for our food and supplies.  My back wa", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " It was difficult", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 35, "question": " I dont think I could last two miles, let alone twelve", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " What else did you do", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 36, "question": " It was difficult", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Well, the second day we went white-water rafting.  Now that was exciting.  W", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 37, "question": " What else did you do", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " He didnt drown, did he", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Well, the second day we went white-water rafting.  Now that was exciting.  W", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No.  Luckily, he was wearing a life jacket", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 42, "question": " He didnt drown, did he", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " That sounds so exciting", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No.  Luckily, he was wearing a life jacket", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": "  It was.  The next day we were so tired.  Hiking and rafting really took a lot ou", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 44, "question": " That sounds so exciting", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " What was the weather like?  Was the water cold", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 48, "question": "  It was.  The next day we were so tired.  Hiking and rafting really took a lot ou", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " No, it was pretty warm.  Its hot there now, like 90 degrees.  It was so nice at th", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": " What was the weather like?  Was the water cold", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " I love water skiing.  Was that your first time", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " No, it was pretty warm.  Its hot there now, like 90 degrees.  It was so nice at th", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Yeah, it was", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " I love water skiing.  Was that your first time", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Could you do it", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yeah, it was", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " The first few tries I just wiped out when the boat started to pull me.  I couldn", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Could you do it", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Yeah, its not hard.  It just takes a little time to learn how to do it.  It sounds like yo", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 60, "question": " The first few tries I just wiped out when the boat started to pull me.  I couldn", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Oh, thats not even all we did.  I havent even told you the best part yet", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yeah, its not hard.  It just takes a little time to learn how to do it.  It sounds like yo", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " What else did you do", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Oh, thats not even all we did.  I havent even told you the best part yet", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Well, the second to last day we went bungee jumping off a bridge", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " What else did you do", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Are you serious", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Well, the second to last day we went bungee jumping off a bridge", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Yep.  Not every one did it because it was pretty scary.  But me and about fiv", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Are you serious", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Youre pretty brave.  I dont think I could have done that", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Yep.  Not every one did it because it was pretty scary.  But me and about fiv", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Ill admit, it was scary.  But, it was so cool.  And, on the last day of the camp, w", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Youre pretty brave.  I dont think I could have done that", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Oh, yeah?  What kind of fish did you catch", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Ill admit, it was scary.  But, it was so cool.  And, on the last day of the camp, w", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Trout.  I caught a 10-pound fish and we all ate what we caught for our last dinne", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Oh, yeah?  What kind of fish did you catch", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " It sounds like you had a great time in Colorado", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Trout.  I caught a 10-pound fish and we all ate what we caught for our last dinne", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I did.  I would definitely recommend an outdoor activity camp", "docId": "08-02", "aSentId": 87, "question": " It sounds like you had a great time in Colorado", "qSentId": 86}]
